{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801598968","data":{"timestamp":" 946801598967"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801606245","data":{"timestamp":" 946801606245"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801614798","data":{"timestamp":" 946801614798"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801620929","data":{"timestamp":" 946801620929"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801630097","data":{"timestamp":" 946801630097"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801636614","data":{"timestamp":" 946801636614"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-10.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801652225","data":{"timestamp":" 946801652225"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801657766","data":{"timestamp":" 946801657766"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801684858","data":{"timestamp":" 946801684858"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801691140","data":{"timestamp":" 946801691139"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801698571","data":{"timestamp":" 946801698571"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801706330","data":{"timestamp":" 946801706330"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801735360","data":{"timestamp":" 946801735360"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801742421","data":{"timestamp":" 946801742421"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801747947","data":{"timestamp":" 946801747947"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801754076","data":{"timestamp":" 946801754075"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 357bcbf2-07e4-48cf-8300-992519fba6d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mnakimbia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801765116","data":{"timestamp":" 946801765116"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alinguruma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINGURUMA"," userResponse":" ALINGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801766190","data":{"timestamp":" 946801766190"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alinguruma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINGURUMA"," userResponse":" ALINGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801771104","data":{"timestamp":" 946801771104"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuwapeleka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801772157","data":{"timestamp":" 946801772157"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuwapeleka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801778691","data":{"timestamp":" 946801778691"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliniambia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIAMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801779773","data":{"timestamp":" 946801779773"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliniambia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALINIAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801790882","data":{"timestamp":" 946801790882"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliyemtaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMTAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801791939","data":{"timestamp":" 946801791938"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliyemtaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMTAKA"," userResponse":" ALIYEMTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801805579","data":{"timestamp":" 946801805579"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumrudisha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMRUDISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801806640","data":{"timestamp":" 946801806640"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumrudisha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMRUDISHA"," userResponse":" KUMRUDISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801827650","data":{"timestamp":" 946801827650"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alichotaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOTAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801828736","data":{"timestamp":" 946801828735"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alichotaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOTAKA"," userResponse":" ALICHOTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801839959","data":{"timestamp":" 946801839959"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMSIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801841015","data":{"timestamp":" 946801841015"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimsikia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMSIKIA"," userResponse":" NILIMSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801850455","data":{"timestamp":" 946801850455"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801851527","data":{"timestamp":" 946801851526"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801861664","data":{"timestamp":" 946801861664"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alipomwona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801862722","data":{"timestamp":" 946801862722"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alipomwona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801873480","data":{"timestamp":" 946801873480"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliufungua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUFUNGUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801874557","data":{"timestamp":" 946801874557"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliufungua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUFUNGUA"," userResponse":" ALIUFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801878358","data":{"timestamp":" 946801878358"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" aliufungua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801878618","data":{"timestamp":" 946801878618"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliufungua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUFUNGUA"," userResponse":" ALIUFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801885375","data":{"timestamp":" 946801885375"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" aliufungua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801895174","data":{"timestamp":" 946801895174"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" aliufungua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801960588","data":{"timestamp":" 946801960587"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" aliufungua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946801990937","data":{"timestamp":" 946801990937"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 18a192b4-586d-4fe7-bb40-9d833f335e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-10.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" aliufungua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802016695","data":{"timestamp":" 946802016695"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802030711","data":{"timestamp":" 946802030711"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802030717","data":{"timestamp":" 946802030717"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" STARTWRITING"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802060159","data":{"timestamp":" 946802060159"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802066371","data":{"timestamp":" 946802066371"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802079487","data":{"timestamp":" 946802079487"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802085192","data":{"timestamp":" 946802085192"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802089334","data":{"timestamp":" 946802089334"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802104271","data":{"timestamp":" 946802104271"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802120369","data":{"timestamp":" 946802120369"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802120374","data":{"timestamp":" 946802120374"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" STARTWRITING"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802136907","data":{"timestamp":" 946802136907"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802154688","data":{"timestamp":" 946802154688"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802160475","data":{"timestamp":" 946802160474"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802167088","data":{"timestamp":" 946802167088"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802172432","data":{"timestamp":" 946802172431"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802177992","data":{"timestamp":" 946802177992"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802181476","data":{"timestamp":" 946802181476"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802184774","data":{"timestamp":" 946802184774"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802188302","data":{"timestamp":" 946802188301"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802191732","data":{"timestamp":" 946802191732"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802194796","data":{"timestamp":" 946802194796"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802198259","data":{"timestamp":" 946802198259"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802201364","data":{"timestamp":" 946802201364"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802206396","data":{"timestamp":" 946802206396"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802210276","data":{"timestamp":" 946802210276"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802214407","data":{"timestamp":" 946802214407"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802218565","data":{"timestamp":" 946802218565"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802222245","data":{"timestamp":" 946802222245"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802227352","data":{"timestamp":" 946802227352"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802241297","data":{"timestamp":" 946802241297"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 96"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802251336","data":{"timestamp":" 946802251335"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 96"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802251668","data":{"timestamp":" 946802251668"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 894e14e4-d9e2-40a3-a3ad-61b0eae0dbcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 96"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802263568","data":{"timestamp":" 946802263568"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802265410","data":{"timestamp":" 946802265410"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802267440","data":{"timestamp":" 946802267440"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802268834","data":{"timestamp":" 946802268834"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802273856","data":{"timestamp":" 946802273856"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802275669","data":{"timestamp":" 946802275669"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802277215","data":{"timestamp":" 946802277215"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802279051","data":{"timestamp":" 946802279051"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802295382","data":{"timestamp":" 946802295382"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802297688","data":{"timestamp":" 946802297688"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802299866","data":{"timestamp":" 946802299866"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802303767","data":{"timestamp":" 946802303767"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802305759","data":{"timestamp":" 946802305758"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802309358","data":{"timestamp":" 946802309358"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802311533","data":{"timestamp":" 946802311533"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802314977","data":{"timestamp":" 946802314977"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802316682","data":{"timestamp":" 946802316682"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802319535","data":{"timestamp":" 946802319535"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802335015","data":{"timestamp":" 946802335015"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802339635","data":{"timestamp":" 946802339635"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802342098","data":{"timestamp":" 946802342098"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802344632","data":{"timestamp":" 946802344631"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802346388","data":{"timestamp":" 946802346388"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802348711","data":{"timestamp":" 946802348710"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802352508","data":{"timestamp":" 946802352507"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802354138","data":{"timestamp":" 946802354138"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802355646","data":{"timestamp":" 946802355645"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802357849","data":{"timestamp":" 946802357849"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802359955","data":{"timestamp":" 946802359955"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802367298","data":{"timestamp":" 946802367297"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802370199","data":{"timestamp":" 946802370199"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802372009","data":{"timestamp":" 946802372009"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802374024","data":{"timestamp":" 946802374024"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802378225","data":{"timestamp":" 946802378225"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802380867","data":{"timestamp":" 946802380867"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802384240","data":{"timestamp":" 946802384240"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802385888","data":{"timestamp":" 946802385888"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802387189","data":{"timestamp":" 946802387189"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802388976","data":{"timestamp":" 946802388976"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802390976","data":{"timestamp":" 946802390976"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802397339","data":{"timestamp":" 946802397339"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802399551","data":{"timestamp":" 946802399551"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802400853","data":{"timestamp":" 946802400853"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802402933","data":{"timestamp":" 946802402933"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802405448","data":{"timestamp":" 946802405448"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802409298","data":{"timestamp":" 946802409298"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802411080","data":{"timestamp":" 946802411080"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802413533","data":{"timestamp":" 946802413533"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802417523","data":{"timestamp":" 946802417523"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802419316","data":{"timestamp":" 946802419316"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802420582","data":{"timestamp":" 946802420582"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802422387","data":{"timestamp":" 946802422387"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802424946","data":{"timestamp":" 946802424946"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802428883","data":{"timestamp":" 946802428882"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802430646","data":{"timestamp":" 946802430645"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802432715","data":{"timestamp":" 946802432715"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802434917","data":{"timestamp":" 946802434917"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802436910","data":{"timestamp":" 946802436910"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802439299","data":{"timestamp":" 946802439298"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802441139","data":{"timestamp":" 946802441139"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802443805","data":{"timestamp":" 946802443805"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802445420","data":{"timestamp":" 946802445420"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802446740","data":{"timestamp":" 946802446740"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802448698","data":{"timestamp":" 946802448697"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802450846","data":{"timestamp":" 946802450846"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802452880","data":{"timestamp":" 946802452880"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802455540","data":{"timestamp":" 946802455540"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802457641","data":{"timestamp":" 946802457641"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802460332","data":{"timestamp":" 946802460332"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802462619","data":{"timestamp":" 946802462619"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802464534","data":{"timestamp":" 946802464533"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802466548","data":{"timestamp":" 946802466548"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802468887","data":{"timestamp":" 946802468887"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIIPENDAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802470994","data":{"timestamp":" 946802470994"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802476717","data":{"timestamp":" 946802476717"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802479046","data":{"timestamp":" 946802479046"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAZIJUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802481557","data":{"timestamp":" 946802481556"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802483073","data":{"timestamp":" 946802483073"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802484835","data":{"timestamp":" 946802484834"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802487787","data":{"timestamp":" 946802487787"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802489816","data":{"timestamp":" 946802489815"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802490161","data":{"timestamp":" 946802490160"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802497528","data":{"timestamp":" 946802497528"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 60fe028f-59f9-4265-a8d7-730f95177ee8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802593381","data":{"timestamp":" 946802593381"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802598566","data":{"timestamp":" 946802598565"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802604218","data":{"timestamp":" 946802604218"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802608183","data":{"timestamp":" 946802608183"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802613565","data":{"timestamp":" 946802613565"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802619670","data":{"timestamp":" 946802619670"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802626487","data":{"timestamp":" 946802626487"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802633005","data":{"timestamp":" 946802633005"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802639770","data":{"timestamp":" 946802639770"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802649993","data":{"timestamp":" 946802649993"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802656241","data":{"timestamp":" 946802656241"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802660960","data":{"timestamp":" 946802660960"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802663773","data":{"timestamp":" 946802663773"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802670045","data":{"timestamp":" 946802670045"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802673297","data":{"timestamp":" 946802673297"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802679913","data":{"timestamp":" 946802679913"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802684834","data":{"timestamp":" 946802684833"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802687349","data":{"timestamp":" 946802687349"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802693322","data":{"timestamp":" 946802693322"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802698813","data":{"timestamp":" 946802698812"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802703724","data":{"timestamp":" 946802703723"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802714264","data":{"timestamp":" 946802714264"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802719134","data":{"timestamp":" 946802719134"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802728835","data":{"timestamp":" 946802728835"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802739772","data":{"timestamp":" 946802739771"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802750639","data":{"timestamp":" 946802750639"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802755425","data":{"timestamp":" 946802755425"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802766924","data":{"timestamp":" 946802766915"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802769250","data":{"timestamp":" 946802769250"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802774250","data":{"timestamp":" 946802774250"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802785211","data":{"timestamp":" 946802785211"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802792625","data":{"timestamp":" 946802792625"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802802661","data":{"timestamp":" 946802802661"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802814330","data":{"timestamp":" 946802814330"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802827910","data":{"timestamp":" 946802827909"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802839430","data":{"timestamp":" 946802839430"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" 639ffbb7-36ad-4ec6-b73c-4859f30fb20e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802871590","data":{"timestamp":" 946802871590"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802875914","data":{"timestamp":" 946802875914"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802877095","data":{"timestamp":" 946802877095"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802881891","data":{"timestamp":" 946802881891"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802882451","data":{"timestamp":" 946802882451"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802886489","data":{"timestamp":" 946802886489"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802892540","data":{"timestamp":" 946802892540"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802894960","data":{"timestamp":" 946802894959"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802898891","data":{"timestamp":" 946802898891"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802903072","data":{"timestamp":" 946802903072"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802904519","data":{"timestamp":" 946802904516"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802908975","data":{"timestamp":" 946802908975"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802909770","data":{"timestamp":" 946802909770"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802914245","data":{"timestamp":" 946802914245"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802919599","data":{"timestamp":" 946802919599"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802920481","data":{"timestamp":" 946802920481"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802929529","data":{"timestamp":" 946802929529"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802930087","data":{"timestamp":" 946802930087"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802940191","data":{"timestamp":" 946802940191"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802944470","data":{"timestamp":" 946802944470"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802951471","data":{"timestamp":" 946802951471"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802957311","data":{"timestamp":" 946802957310"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802961228","data":{"timestamp":" 946802961228"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802966189","data":{"timestamp":" 946802966188"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802969847","data":{"timestamp":" 946802969846"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802975309","data":{"timestamp":" 946802975308"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802983256","data":{"timestamp":" 946802983255"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802988631","data":{"timestamp":" 946802988630"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802991237","data":{"timestamp":" 946802991237"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946802994585","data":{"timestamp":" 946802994585"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803000128","data":{"timestamp":" 946803000127"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803013773","data":{"timestamp":" 946803013772"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803021829","data":{"timestamp":" 946803021828"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" d6be80f0-8ead-4cb8-8a53-2b6d56000e9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803050123","data":{"timestamp":" 946803050123"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803057034","data":{"timestamp":" 946803057034"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803063237","data":{"timestamp":" 946803063237"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803069246","data":{"timestamp":" 946803069246"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803074041","data":{"timestamp":" 946803074041"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803077328","data":{"timestamp":" 946803077328"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803081940","data":{"timestamp":" 946803081940"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803087264","data":{"timestamp":" 946803087264"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803089152","data":{"timestamp":" 946803089152"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803093203","data":{"timestamp":" 946803093203"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803097019","data":{"timestamp":" 946803097019"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803098999","data":{"timestamp":" 946803098999"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803103766","data":{"timestamp":" 946803103766"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803110983","data":{"timestamp":" 946803110983"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803114188","data":{"timestamp":" 946803114188"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803118104","data":{"timestamp":" 946803118104"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803123015","data":{"timestamp":" 946803123015"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803126634","data":{"timestamp":" 946803126634"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803129995","data":{"timestamp":" 946803129995"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803131619","data":{"timestamp":" 946803131618"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803133374","data":{"timestamp":" 946803133374"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803138108","data":{"timestamp":" 946803138108"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803142692","data":{"timestamp":" 946803142692"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803143395","data":{"timestamp":" 946803143395"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803147446","data":{"timestamp":" 946803147445"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803149454","data":{"timestamp":" 946803149454"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803153470","data":{"timestamp":" 946803153470"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803157532","data":{"timestamp":" 946803157532"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803158270","data":{"timestamp":" 946803158270"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803162341","data":{"timestamp":" 946803162340"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803170016","data":{"timestamp":" 946803170016"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803172152","data":{"timestamp":" 946803172151"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803180449","data":{"timestamp":" 946803180448"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803185048","data":{"timestamp":" 946803185048"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803197255","data":{"timestamp":" 946803197255"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803204094","data":{"timestamp":" 946803204081"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803212007","data":{"timestamp":" 946803212007"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803226792","data":{"timestamp":" 946803226791"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803234394","data":{"timestamp":" 946803234394"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803269067","data":{"timestamp":" 946803269067"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946803277393","data":{"timestamp":" 946803277393"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_112038"," gameId":" ed618b03-9543-4a8b-a8c2-d44f6217324f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}